Roy wood
J if you want more people to stand for
the anthem change the
song as long as we stand and agree that
people died for us to kick it we can do
that to any song you can do that to
Bruno Mars let's be real about the
anthem first and foremost the beat is
whack it don't go hard you love America
but you ain't downloaded the national
anthem to your phone a't but one person
successfully Escape me to allegations
and that's Hugh Hefner he
died which I got to say well played did
not see that coming America is a
restaurant that sells equality and some
of y'all had some delicious equality it
was good you had great
service and some of us need to speak to
a manager
[Applause]